http://www.uniquegardendecor.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
Sign In
Forgot your password?
View Messages ()
View Order Status
Completed
Return Requests
Your Address Book
Wish Lists ()
Yard Art Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy Applies to www.uiniquegardendecor.com and Yard Art, and governs data collection and usage. For thepurposes of this privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Yard Art include www.uniquegardendecor.com and Yard Art. The Yard Art website is an Ecommerce site. By using the Yard Art website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal InformationYard Art may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If youpurchase Yard Art's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected byYard Art. This information can include : Your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain the quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Yard Art website.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Yard Art's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.Yard Art encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Yard Art so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Yard At is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Yard Art website.
Use of your personal informationYard Art collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
Yard Art may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Yard Art affiliates. Yard Art does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Yard Art may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, sendyou email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Yard Art, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Yard Art may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Yard Art in order to determine what Yard Art services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Yard Art to customers whose behavior indicates they are interested in a particular subject area.Yard Art will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Yard Art or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Yard Art; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Yard Art, or the public.
Use of CookiesThe Yard Art website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issues the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Yard Art pages, or register with Yard Art or services, a cookie helps Yard Art to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Yard Art website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Yard Art features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Yard Art services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal InformationTo secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, Yard Art uses the following :
GeoTrustWhen personal information(such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer(SSL) protocol.
Children Under ThirteenYard Art does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Opt-Out & UnsubscribeWe respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Yard Art by contacting us here:
- web page : www.uniquegardendecor.com
- Email : help@uniquegardendecor.com
- Phone : 925 234-3153
Changes to this Statement
Yard Art will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Yard Art encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Yard Art is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Yard Art welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy, If you believe that Yard Art has not adhered to this Statement please contact Yard Art at :
Yard Art117 Town and Country Blvd.Suite CDanville, CA 94526
Email Address:help@uniquegardendecor.com
Telephone Number:925 234-3153
Effective as of January 1, 2007
Contact Info
117-C Town and Country Drive
Danville, California 94526
866-382-8600
Get $50 off when you sign up for our mailing list!
Copyright 2020 Yard Art. All Rights Reserved.
All prices are in USD.
Sitemap
View Cart
Go To Checkout
